ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Label Chorus. New York Auditions, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 142)
- Union Label Chorus. New York Auditions (Box 25, Folder 143)
- Union Label Chorus. Chicago Auditions, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 144)
  November
- ILGWU members audition - Retired Working Mother Audition (Box 25, Folder 145)
  Union label commercial
- ILGWU members - Retired Working Mother (Box 25, Folder 146)
  Union label commercial auditions
- Lillian Armor - Out Takes Union Lable Working Woman; "Buy Takes", 1975 (Box 25, Folder 147)
  October; Union label commercial
- Lillian Armor and Emma Daukko - Out Takes Union Label Retired Working mother.; "Buy takes", 1975 (Box 25, Folder 148)
- 1975 Chorus Out Takes - Lillian Chorus (Box 25, Folder 149)
  October; Union label commercial; Paula Green Advertising in Conjunction with NBC Productions
- Union label commercials. Grandmother-granddaughter who work together in the garment industry - spot out takes. Union Label Commercial., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 150)
  3/4" U-MATIC; 10 min.; February 1976
- Union label commercials. Grandmother-granddaughter who work together in the garment industry spot out takes. Union Label Commercial, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 151)
  3/4" U-MATIC; December 1976
- Union label commercials. Betty And James Bledsoe 2, Working Couple Union Label., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 154)
  3/4" U-MATIC; 44 min.; September 1976
- Union label commercials. Phyllis Thiem in out takes for Union Label Commercial., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 155)
  3/4" U-Matic; 20 min.; October 1976
- 1977 Chorus Indoor. Paula Green Advertising Out Takes ILGWU. (Box 25, Folder 159)
  August; Union label commercials
- Meridith Gatewood, Lydia Harrell - Out Takes - Blouses Segments., 1977 (Box 25, Folder 160)
- Lydia Harrell Billboard Shots, Out Takes Blouses Spots., 1977 (Box 25, Folder 161)
  September; Union label commercials
- 1979 Chorus Out Takes Union Label Song (Box 25, Folder 162)
- Union label commercials. Jim Prine - Out Takes for ILGWU Union Label Commercial, Import Spots., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 156)
  3/4" U-Matic; 60 min.; October 1976
- Union label commercials. 1977 Chorus Outdoor ILGWU Union Label Series take 1-34. (Box 26, Folder 158)
  3/4" U-Matic; 60 min.; August 1977
- Union Label commercials. 1977 Chorus Indoor. Paula Greene Advertising Out Takes ILGWU (Box 26, Folder 159)
- Union Label commercials. Meredith Gatewood, Lydia Harrell - Out Takes - "Blouses" segments, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 160)
- Union Label commercials. Lydia Harrell Billboard Shots, Out Takes, "Blouses" spots, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 161)
  3/4" U-Matic; 45 min.; September 1977
- 1979 Chorus Out Takes Union Label Song (Box 26, Folder 162)
  3/4" U-Matic; 50 min.; October 1979
- 1979 Chorus Out Takes, Union Label Song (Box 26, Folder 163)
  3/4" U-Matic; 18 min.; October 1979
- Union label commercials. Americans Helping Americans - Union Label., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 164)
  3/4" U-MATIC; 60 min.; November 1982
- Union label commercials. Americans Helping Americans - Union Label (middle-aged white woman).; SMPTE Burn in-Takes 95 to 127, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 165)
  3/4" U-Matic; 19 min.; November 19, 1982
- Union label commercials. SMPTE Burn in Take 128 to final; Americans Helping Americans - Union Label (older woman, younger couple). (Box 26, Folder 166)
  3/4" U-Matic; 24 min.
- Union label commercials. Emma Dauko., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 167)
  3/4" U-MATIC; 5 min.; November 1975
- Union label commercials. Grandmother-granddaughter who work together in the garment industry - spot out takes., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 168)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1 min.; February 1976
- Union label commercials. Lillian and Emma, Grandmother-granddaughter work together, spot out takes., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 169)
  3/4" U- Matic; 3 min.; April 1976
- Union label commercials. Lillian and Emma, Grandmother-granddaughter work together, spot out takes., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 170)
- Lillian Doral, Emma Dauko - Union Label working woman, retired working mother, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 171)
  Nov.; Union label commercials
- Steve And Grace Barbee Et. Al., Young Working Couple, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 172)
  Sep.; Union label commercials
- Grandmother-granddaughter work together in the garment industry - spot out takes, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 173)
  Oct.; Union label commercials
- Jim Prine, Phyllis Thiem - Imports Spots, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 174)
- Jim Prine Imports and Grandmother- Granddaughter, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 175)
- Meridith Gatewood Union Label Commercial - 2 Blouse Segment (Box 27, Folder 176)
  Sept.; Union label commercials
- Meridith Gatewood Union Label Commercial, Blouse Segment Final, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 177)
- Jim Prine on Imports, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 178)
- Betty And James Bledsoe, Working Couple, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 179)
- Jim Prine, Imports, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 180)
  Jan. 6; Union label commercials
- Jim Prine II Imports (Box 27, Folder 181)
- Jim Prine II w/ Indoor Chorus (Box 27, Folder 182)
- Jim Prine III w/ Indoor Chorus, Rebecca with Handclaps New Mix, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 183)
  Jan. 10; Union label commercials
- Union label commercials. Norma II w/ Indoor Chorus, Norma II w/Outdoor Chorus., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 184)
  3/4" U-Matic; 2 min.; Marrch 1978; 2 copies
- Union label commercials. Norma 2 w/ Indoor Chorus., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 185)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1 min.; March 1978
- Union label commercials. Bledsoe and Norma, Working Couple, Union Label., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 186)
  3/4" U-Matic; 30 sec.; September 1978
- Union label commercials. Betty And James Bledsoe, Working Couple Union Label w/Chorus III., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 187)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1 min.; September 1976
- Union label commercials. Betty And James Bledsoe, Working Couple Union Label w/Chorus III., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 188)
- Union label commercials. Voncile Song we Sing" Chorus 3., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 189)
  3/4" U-Matic; 30 sec.; July 1981
- Union label commercials. Song we Sing III, Chorus 3 (African-American, 2 White Women talk)., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 190)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1 min.; July 1981
- Union label commercials. Song we Sing - Joan, Helen, Voncile, Chorus 3., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 191)
  3/4" U-Matic; 2 min.; July 1981; 2 copies
- Union label commercials. Lillian, Georgia, Voncile, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 192)
  3/4" U-Matic; 3 min.; November 1982
- Union label commercials. Voting. Final Version, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 193)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1 min.; November 1984
- Union label commercials. Beverly, Kathy And Joan - Clothes In Your Closet, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 194)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1.5 min.; November 1982
- Union label commercials. Georgia from Kilgore, TX. (Box 28, Folder 195)
  3/4" U-Matic; 60 min.
- Union label commercials. Crafted With Pride - All Stars Revue, Made In USA. OJ Simpson, Sammy Davis Jr., James Caan., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 196)
  3/4" U-Matic; 1.3 min.; March 1986
- Union label commercials. "Imports," Phyllis Thiem (Box 29, Folder 155)
- ILGWU Commercial - WNBC TV News, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 197)
  August; Union Label, Reporter Talks with Union Label Chorus Members
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta Auditions, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 198)
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta Auditions, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 199)
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta auditions, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 200)
- Union Label Chorus. New York Auditions, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 203)
- Sunbelt, Snow Belt Editorial, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 204)
  pril; Peter Kohler expresses misgivings about restricting trade through tariffs or quotas, except for garment industry, the biggest employer of law-wage, low-skilled jobs in New York City. Argues to limit imports, provide job retraining
- Garment Industry, Fashion Industry Reports, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 205)
  May; WXPIX, WCPS
- Fashion Industry Ten O'clock News, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 206)
  May; WNEW
- Fashion Industry and NY State Theatre, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 207)
  May; WABC
- Sweatshops., 1981 (Box 29, Folder 208)
  March; Richard wagner finds poor working conditions and law pay in garment sweatshops, fire code violations, union contracts ignored and illegal immigrants employed; CBS News
- Homework, CBS News, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 209)
  April; 1938 Federal Labor Standards Act made homework illegal, (full day in the sweatshop then extra work done home at night). Interview with Sol Chaikin. Chinese Americans and workers, economic and social issues in garment industry, homework, immigration.
- NY Eyewitness News Tom Ellis - recent problems in the garment industry, imports, exported jobs, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 210)
- Union image, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 211)
  May; $4 miillion union lable ad campaign to correct the pub,ic image, interviews paula Green producer/director of ads, and Sol Chaikin
- King Tut. Palo Alto exhibit, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 212)
- Eyewitness News, NY segment - problems confronting unions, cheap foreign imports, organizing new workers, questions of corruption, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 213)
- Eyewitness News - Labor Day, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 214)
- Auto Workers ILGWU Union Controversy, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 215)
  July
- The Taiwan Connection, Little Rock, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 216)
  September; potential soybean deal between Arkansas and Taiwan to reduce trade deficit. ILGWU concerned about cheap, imported Taiwanese garments.
- Jane Fondas workout clothes made by ILGWU, MADE IN USA., 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 217)
- History of the labor movement and unionization, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 218)
  May; incl. AFL, AFL-CIO merger formation, Wagner Act, Taft-Hartley Act, Right-to-work laws.
- AFL-CIO Meeting - Building Unionism, Membership, Economics, Media Coverage, Union Label., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 219)
- Billboards. Atlanta., 1979 (Box 30, Folder 220)
- Heroin: Chasing the Dragon. Geraldo Rivera, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 221)
  December; drug production and sale in Afghanistan, Iran, and Pakistan.
- News garment industry, from various TV stations, interviews and debates about different industrial unions, auto workers, circus workers. (Box 30, Folder 222)
- Circus Workers In Unions. ILGWU Union Label Song, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 223)
- Sol Chaikin on the Today Show, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 224)
  December; debate between Chaikin and Ray Garcia (VP of the Committee for International Trade) on trade deficit and imports.
- Sol Chaikin on Good Morning America responds to President Jimmy Carters anti-inflationary program, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 225)
- Sol Chaikin on Good Morning America comments on President Carters anti-inflationary program, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 226)
  November; AFL-CIO critique of program, wage freezes, and prices.
- Sol Chaikin seconds Jimmy Carters nomination at the Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 227)
- Sol Chaikin on the Today Show with Tom Brokaw, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 228)
  September; talks about the history of the ILGWU, union problems, international unionism, imports, union label.
- Sol Chaikin on Good Morning America, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 229)
  November; minimum wage, productivity.
- NYC Golden Apple Award in Design for redesigning the NY Police Department uniforms, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 230)
  November; Halston Midday Live WNEW
- Triangle Factory Fire; People, Places, and Things, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 231)
  Saturday, March 18; WABC TV CH 7
- State of the Unions, Boston, PBS In Search of the Real America, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 232)
  July; looks at labor before unions and the industrial revolution; interview with Milton Friedman.
- Labor Footage for Spectacular Logo., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 233)
- COTACO. COPIA ILGWU. Puerto Rico. (Puerto Rican Consumer Affairs Committee) COPIA (ILGWU), 1980 (Box 31, Folder 234)
  The American Center for Food, Wine and Arts, ILGWU. Puerto Rico, consumer group, product safety, health care, environment, nutrition.
- Preview of 1982 NAPKE Convention (Box 31, Folder 235)
  March; primetime access rules, if repealed, would allow networks more discretion regarding programming.
- Union presentation - effort to increase TV ads by union, to boost public opinion of unions, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 236)
  with clips from ads by AFSCME, AFL-CIO, CWA, Building and Construction Trade Council, Illinois Education Association
- Bicentennial Minute: Sol Chaikin on US History, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 237)
- Voting" "Statue (VHS), 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  August 13; Union label commercials; Video of the Statue of Liberty fading into the faces of four women - "This is the face of Liberty and mine is too."
- Union label commercials. "Clothes in your Closet," "Song we Sing." (Box 32, Folder 2)
  VHS; August 19, 1986
- ILGWU on the Move- Belonging to a Union, the World of ILGWU, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  VHS; 13 min.
- With These Hands, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  VHS; 50 min.; Fictional account of an ILGWU member from 1910. Based on history, includes Triangle Fire, and legislation. Goes through Great Depression and New Deal.; Director and Producer: Jack Arnold. Nominated for best documentary feature, 1950.
- Garment Industry. CBC Journal Documentary., 1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  BETA; October 20, 1983
- Day Care Center in Chinatown (VHS) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  WABC, WCBS
- NBE Productions, YGW (VHS), 1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Commercials on film., 1980 (Box 32, Folder 148)
  October 13; 6 films
- Music tracks on film (Box 32, Folder 149)
  32mm; 9 films
- With These Hands., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 238)
  Fictional account of an ILGWU member from 1910. Based on history, includes Triangle Fire, and legislation. Goes through Great Depression and New Deal.; Director and Producer: Jack Arnold. Nominated for best documentary feature, 1950.
- With These Hands., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 238b)
  Fictional account of an ILGWU member
- Sol Chaikin on Herman Badillos Urban Journal QandA, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 239)
  December; on imports, protectionism, declining membership.
- Camera Three; WCBS-TV, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 240)
  July 30
- #664 Look Good, #665 Easter Parade, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  April 2; 7.5 IPS
- Spanish Difference with live announcer, ILG 630, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  March 17; 7.5 IPS
- #662 An American Christmas, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  February 6; Radio 7.5 IPS
- #672 Washington Veto, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  July 18; Radio 7.5 IPS
- #0120 Gloria Look for the Union Label, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  April 3
- #671 Washington Veto, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  :50 pre-recorded, :10 live
- #671 Washington Veto, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  July 18; :50 pre-recorded, :10 live
- Down Home, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Debussy Etude (Box 33, Folder 9)
  For xxGD 0115 original music "Together with Gerard Courtin [sp?]
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Spanish Version, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  " x 7" audio reel
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Spanish Version, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  " x 7"
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Spanish Version (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Spanish Version, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Chinese Version, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, English Version, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, English Version, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, English Version (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, English Version (Box 34, Folder 9)
  " x 7"; 4 copies
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Chinese Version, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  " x 7"; 2 copies
- ILGWU Local 23, Filmstrip, English Version, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Your Union and You LaBelle Master, Spanish Version (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Meet Your Union LaBelle Beeped, Spanish Version, 1964 (Box 34a, Folder 1)
  " x 7"; August 26, 1964
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Chinese Version, 1973-1975 (Box 34a, Folder 2)
  " x 7"; 5 copies
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, English Version, 1974 (Box 34a, Folder 3)
- Your Union and You Local 23-25, Spanish Version, 1973 (Box 34a, Folder 4)
  " x 7"; June 29
- [Untitled] (Box 34a, Folder 5)
- [Untitled] (Box 34a, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Chinese version (Box 34a, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Chinese version for La Belle (Box 34a, Folder 8)
- "Meet Your Union" English (La Belle bleeped), 1974 (Box 34a, Folder 9)
  " x 7"; August 26, 1974
- Garment workers spot, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  7.5 IPS, includes letter from Ed Bell to Jerry Kaufman, 11/8/79: "Enclosed is the "Union Label" news feature we did during the auditions here in Boston. []"
- ILGWU Radio spots, 1. Years Ago 2. Like a Job? 3. Question (Box 36, Folder 2a-c)
- ILGWU Radio, 1. Grandmother/Granddaughter, Version A, GD 591, 2. Grandmother/Granddaughter, Version B, GD 590, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  June 26
- Georgia, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  February 28; Unedited direct from video, 2" to ", 7.5 IPS, YGW 0131, Spokeswoman audio only (no chorus)
- ILGWU, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Radio; 60 second mix; new radio mix,, vocal mix, #579; November 25, 1975
- ILGWU, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  TV mix only, October 29, 1975
- #580 Emma Retired (Box 36, Folder 580)
  7.5 IPS
- #594 Doris Trolley (Box 36, Folder 594)
- #597 The Bledsoes (Box 36, Folder 597)
- #606 1.The Bledsoes 2. Jim PrineImports version I 3. The BarbeesYoung Couple (Box 36, Folder 606)
- #608 MagdalenaSpanish Working Mother, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 608)
  November 15; 4 copies; 7.5 IPS
- #609 1. The Bledsoes (GDIL 0102) 2. Doris Tolley (ID 594) 3. The Barbees (GDIL 0101) (Box 36, Folder 609)
- #615 Jim Prine (Box 36, Folder 615)
- #618 Jim Prine #2 with new 177 chorus (Box 36, Folder 618)
- #619 Magdalena with new 177 chorus (Box 36, Folder 619)
  4 copies; 7.5 IPS
- #620 MeredithBlouses, New Chorus, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 620)
- #621 NormaChristmas Shopper, New Chorus, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 621)
  November 11; 7.5 IPS
- #623 IsabelleSpanish Christmas Shopper, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 623)
  November 21; 7.5 IPS; 6 copies
- #625 Pre-Easter Emma #78 with New Chorus, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 625)
  February 17; 7.5 IPS
- #627 Connie Easter #78 (Box 36, Folder 627)
- #631 Bands 1, 2, 3 Identical Original Chorus, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 631)
  August 13
- #633 Emma II with New Chorus (Bernie with handclaps) (Box 36, Folder 633)
- #634 Barbees with New Chorus (Bernie with handclaps) (Box 36, Folder 634)
- #636 Emma Shopping, Norman Christmas Shopper, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 636)
- #637 Original Chorus, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 637)
- #641Connie" (with old chorus) (Box 36, Folder 641)
- #642 Meredith (with old chorus) (Box 36, Folder 642)
- #645 Norma Christmas Shopper with Chorus III, #654 Voncile - Chorus III, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 645)
  November 20, 1980
- #645 Norma Christmas Shopper with Chorus III, #654 VoncileChorus III, 1979 (Box 36a, Folder 645)
  November 5; 7.5 IPS; 2 copies
- #646 Emma Shopping with Chorus; #645 Norma Christmas Shopper with Chorus III; #647 Meredith Chorus III, 1979 (Box 36a, Folder 646)
  November 5; 7.5 IPS; 11 copies
- #648 Isabelle Christmas Shopper Chorus III, Spanish, 1979 (Box 36a, Folder 648)
  November 13; 7.5 IPS; 7 copies
- #652 Carmen Chorus III, 1979 (Box 36a, Folder 652)
  November 5; 7.5 IPS; 5 copies
- #653 Chorus III, New radio mix, 1980 (Box 36a, Folder 653)
  February 12
- #654 VoncileChorus III; #645 Norma Christmas Shopper with Chorus III, 1980 (Box 36a, Folder 654)
  November 20; 7.5 IPS; 7 copies
- #654 VoncileChorus III; #655 Norma, Christmas ShoppersChorus III; #656 ConnieChorus III, 1980 (Box 36a, Folder 655)
  #654, November 20; 7.5 IPS; #655, November 20; 7.5 IPS; #656, March 4; 7.5 IPS
- #656 ConnieChorus III, 1980 (Box 36a, Folder 656)
  March 4; 7.5 IPS
- #654 VoncileChorus III; #655 Norma, Christmas ShoppersChorus III; #656 ConnieChorus III, 1980 (Box 36b, Folder 654)
  #654, November 20; 7.5 IPS; #655, November 20; 7.5 IPS; #656, March 4; 7.5 IPS; 11 copies
- box contained cassettes, they were removed and placed in media case; microfilm from this box now makes up 5780/192 mf (Box 37)
  - Leon Stein/Unity #1, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; May 30, 1978
  - David Dubinsky-Stulberg memoirs (Box 230, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette
  - David DubinskyFrustrations of retirement; politics (confidential) (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - David DubinskyAJ Goldberg (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - PAMrs. Jessup, Roscho, Ceil (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - PAJo, Pennsylvania (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Celia, Al/Al, Phyllis; Phyllis, Mac/Phil, Mac; Hope, Anna; Anna (Box 235, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; 3 parts
  - David Dubinsky: #3, Henry Uviller; #4, Dubinsky-Alex Rose (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #5, Fight with CP; #6, Personal/Hillman (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #7, Hillman (continued); #8, I.M.P.C.H.M.N. (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #9, Miscellaneous; #10, Lovestone (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #11, Lovestone; #12, Lovestone (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #13, Rackets; #14, Rackets (continued) (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #15, Labor Secretary Arthur J. Goldberg, John F. Kennedy, Corruption; #16, Finance (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #17, Harry Lang; #18, Harry Lang (continued) (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #19, Philosophy, politics, ICFTU (International Confederation of Free Trade Unions); #20, ICFTU (continued), strikes, Crown prince (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #21, Knippel, Powell, Wage rates; #22, Heightstown, Aeta, Ehrlich (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #23, Medina-Zim[merman?] debate on Franklin D. Roosevelt; #24, Miscellaneous (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #25, Elnana report, training institute; #26, ? (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #27, Union First to Engineer Department; #28, Union First, FDR, Foundation, Heightstown (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #29, Russia, Communists; #30, Union Economic Standards, Officers (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #31, ?; #32, Truman, etc. (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #33, Emil Schlesinger; #36, Charles Zimmerman, part 1 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #34, Emil Schlesinger; #35, Emil Schlesinger (continued) (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #37, Charles Zimmerman, part 2; #38, Charles Zimmerman, part 3 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #39, Charles Zimmerman, part 4; #40, Charles Zimmerman; part 5 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #41, Charles Zimmerman, part 6; #42, Industrial relations (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #44, Alex Rose, part 1; #45, Alex Rose, part 2 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #46, Alex Rose, part 3; #47, Alex Rose, part 4 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - David Dubinsky: #48, George Meany, Commodore Hotel; #49, George Meany, Commodore Hotel, 1970 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; December 14, 1970
- American Fashion Now, presented by the ILGWU (Box 39, Folder 1)
- The ILGWU presents The Many Lengths of Fashions (side A), Coats and Suits for You (side B) (Box 39, Folder 2)
- My Name is Mary Brown A musical narrative, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Revised Narrative, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  September 22
- Convention film, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  September 12
- ILGWU Convention, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  Harrison production, includes opening, partial Stulberg speech, Rustin
- Close-ups, group shots, active retirees button shots (Box 39.5, Folder 1)
  Slides
- Medium shots (Box 39.5, Folder 2)
- Social services, New York exteriors, 275 7th Avenue sequence, computers, phone sequence (Box 39.5, Folder 3)
- Union ties, Loneliness, Grace, Leisure time (Box 39.5, Folder 4)
- Pre-retirement seminar, maps, With our retirees (Box 39.5, Folder 5)
- Hands, life membership card, ILG logo, sewing machines, archive logo, active retiree buttons, ILG logo/Life membership card (Box 39.5, Folder 6)
- Club med, Diplomat hotel, Alice, E.T., fabric, hand sewn label, Retired stamp, baby face (Box 39.5, Folder 7)
- Retiree quiz, What is a retiree, paintings, car, organs, oldest man, activities (Box 39.5, Folder 8)
- Meetings, capitols, slogans, plane with banner, food drive, telethon, chorus, documents/testimony (Box 39.5, Folder 9)